Milan Biswakarma
CSE 4344-002
Assignment# 1
9th March, 2018

ReadMe File

The program was written in java using Netbeans as IDE. 
All the files should be in same folder for the program to run. 
The port number used for this program is 8090
The html file should be named as 'index.html'

To run the program:
 1. Run Networks.java. The message ' Ready to Connect' is displayed.
 2. Run the index.html in the browser using by typing 'localhost:8090/index.html'.Thus, the content is displayed in the browser.
If any other name except index.html is typed then HTTP ERROR 404 is displayed.